<Namespace Name="Microsoft.SqlServer.Server">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="64061d05f0af9b3db3f48f1742ff8a085c4f71d8" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="df6cf590aa3087f6c7c202712eee781c6a3c8f96" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ja-JP" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="05/10/2018" />
    <Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30724696" />
  </Metadata>
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-101">
        <see cref="N:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server" /> 名前空間には、Microsoft .NET Framework 共通言語ランタイム (CLR: Common Language Runtime) を Microsoft SQL Server および SQL Server データベース エンジン プロセスの実行環境に統合するために特有のクラス、インターフェイス、および列挙体が含まれています。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="a6da6-101">The <see cref="N:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server" /> namespace contains classes, interfaces, and enumerations that are specific to the integration of the Microsoft .NET Framework common language runtime (CLR) into Microsoft SQL Server, and the SQL Server database engine process execution environment.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-102">内のクラス属性を使用して、 <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server> (スカラーおよびテーブル値)、ユーザー定義関数、いずれかで、ユーザー定義集計関数には、.NET Framework の言語がサポートされている名前空間、ストアド プロシージャ、トリガー、ユーザー定義型を作成できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-102">Using the attribute classes in the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server> namespace, you can create stored procedures, triggers, user-defined types, user-defined functions (both scalar and table-valued), and user-defined aggregate functions in any supported .NET Framework language.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-103">SQL Server にも登録できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-103">You can also register them in SQL Server.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-104">クエリ、<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext>クラスを SQL Server データベース エンジン プロセスで現在実行中のコードが実行されているかどうかを判断します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-104">Query the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext> class to determine whether the currently executing code is running in the SQL Server database engine process.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-105">これは、ユーザーがサーバーで、マネージ ストアド プロシージャまたは関数を呼び出したときに、またはユーザーの操作には、マネージ コード トリガーが起動されたときに、呼び出し元のコンテキストも提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-105">This also provides the caller's context when a user calls a managed stored procedure or function on the server, or when a user's action fires a managed code trigger.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-106"><xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext>クラスを提供、 <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlPipe> 、使用される結果はから返されたオブジェクトをクライアントに、ストアド プロシージャ、<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlTriggerContext>起動されるトリガーを原因となった操作に関する情報を提供するオブジェクトと<xref:System.Security.Principal.WindowsIdentity>クライアントが認証の統合セキュリティを使用する場合は、呼び出し元のクライアントの id を確認するために使用できるオブジェクト。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-106">The <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlContext> class provides a <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlPipe> object, through which results are returned to the client from a stored procedure, a <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server.SqlTriggerContext> object, which provides information about the operation that caused a trigger to be fired, and a <xref:System.Security.Principal.WindowsIdentity> object, which can be used to determine the identity of the calling client when the client used integrated security for authentication.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="a6da6-107">SQL Server の CLR 統合と、Api の詳細については、<xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server>名前空間には、SQL Server オンライン ブックを参照してください。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="a6da6-107">For more information about SQL Server CLR integration and the APIs in the <xref:Microsoft.SqlServer.Server> namespace, see SQL Server Books Online.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>