<Namespace Name="System.Net.PeerToPeer">
  <Metadata><Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="320f5d11742848ae51a1bbb18f46ae6b439a5235" /><Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="434f60616a9793fa8436744549fc856e94f7a648" /><Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" /><Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ja-JP" /><Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="08/24/2018" /><Meta Name="ms.locfileid" Value="30734756" /></Metadata><Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="f1c12-101"><see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> 名前空間は、ピア ネットワーク機能を使用できるようにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-101">The <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> namespace provides access to peer networking functionality.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-102">ピアが互いを検出して識別子を解決する方法は、一時的な接続とアドレスのドメイン ネーム システム (DNS) などのレコードへのアクセスがないことをする複雑になります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-102">How peers discover each other and resolve identifiers is complicated by transient connectivity and the lack of access to address records such as the Domain Name System (DNS).</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-103">Windows ピア ツー ピア インフラストラクチャでは、PNRP と呼ばれる名前解決とピア検出スキームにより、この問題は解決します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-103">The Windows Peer-to-Peer Infrastructure solves this problem with a name resolution and peer discovery scheme called PNRP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-104">ピア名解決プロトコル (PNRP) は、ピア ツー ピア ネットワークの名前解決メカニズムを提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-104">Peer Name Resolution Protocol (PNRP) provides a name resolution mechanism for peer-to-peer networks.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-105">PNRP がネットワークに名前を解決するように設計<xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint>完全にピア ツー ピア方式でします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-105">PNRP is designed to resolve a name to a network <xref:System.Net.IPEndPoint> in a completely peer-to-peer manner.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-106">基本的な PNRP の機能が提供される、<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer>名前空間のクラス。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-106">Basic PNRP functionality is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer> namespace classes.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-107">ピアを作成し、内に登録する機能を提供する<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud>ピア。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-107">They provide the ability to create a peer and register it in a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Cloud> of peers.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-108">解決する機能も用意されて、<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName>にそのネットワーク エンドポイント、TCP ポート、クラウド、またはその他のアドレスの識別子。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-108">They also provide the ability to resolve a <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.PeerName> to its network endpoint, TCP port, cloud, or other address identifier(s).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-109">ピア ツー ピア ネットワー キングの高度な機能が提供される、<xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration>名前空間。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-109">Advanced functionality for peer-to-peer networking is provided in the <xref:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration> namespace.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-110">Windows Vista では、PNRP は、アプリケーションがオンデマンドで開始されるサービスとして同梱されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-110">In Windows Vista, PNRP ships as a service that is started on demand by applications.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-111">さらに、リモート接続および通信用のコンピューター名を公開する場合にアプリケーションまたはユーザーが手動で有効にできる、PNRP コンピューターの登録サービスがあります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-111">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service that can be manually enabled by applications or users if they want to publish machine names for remote connections and communications.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-112">PNRP バージョン 1 は、Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2)、Windows XP Professional x64 Edition、および Windows XP Service Pack 1 (SP1)、および、Advanced Networking Pack for Windows XP に含まれていました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-112">PNRP version 1 was included in Windows XP Service Pack 2 (SP2), Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, and Windows XP with Service Pack 1 (SP1) and the Advanced Networking Pack for Windows XP.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="f1c12-113">さらに、リモート接続および通信のためのコンピューター名を公開に関心がある場合にアプリケーション/ユーザーが手動で有効にできる PNRP コンピューターの登録サービスがあります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="f1c12-113">In addition, there is a PNRP machine registration service which can be manually enabled by applications/users if there is interest in publishing machine names for remote connection and communication.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>