<Namespace Name="System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="93bdf-101"><see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" /> 名前空間は、<see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> のネットワーク機能を強化し、サーバーに依存しない管理されたコラボレーション セッションを実現するための機能を提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-101">The <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer.Collaboration" /> namespace enhances <see cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" /> networking functionality and provides capabilities for serverless managed collaboration sessions.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-102">ピア ツー ピア (P2P) コラボレーション インフラストラクチャでは、ネットワーク ゲーム見合い、会議、対話型の他の参加者が複数のアクティビティなどの共同作業のピア ツー ピア ネットワーク ベースのフレームワークを提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-102">The Peer-to-Peer (P2P) Collaboration Infrastructure provides a peer-to-peer network-based framework for collaborative activities, such as network game matchmaking, conferencing, and other interactive multi-participant activities.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-103">このサーバーなしのインフラストラクチャには、手順を簡易化するアプリケーションがサーバーなしのピアのプレゼンスを追跡、参加要素への招待を送信、同じサブネット上のピアの検出を連絡先の管理 Api が含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-103">This serverless infrastructure includes APIs that simplify the process by which applications can track peer presence without a server, send invitations to participants, discover peers on the same subnet, and manage contacts.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-104">ピア コラボレーションのネイティブの Api は、32 ビットおよび 64 ビット エディションで Windows Vista クライアントで利用可能です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-104">Native Peer Collaboration APIs are available on Windows Vista clients in both 32-bit and 64-bit editions.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-105">ピア コラボレーションの Api は、Windows Server 2008 でご利用いただけません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-105">Peer Collaboration APIs are not available on Windows Server 2008.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-106">メモ: コラボレーション Api は、サービスから機能、サービスは、呼び出し元を偽装して、呼び出し元が (組み込みのユーザー) ではなく、対話ユーザーである場合にのみ。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-106">NOTE: The Collaboration APIs are functional from a service only if the service is impersonating a caller, and the caller is an interactive user (as opposed to a built-in user).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="93bdf-107">複数の連絡先のマネージャーがサポートされていません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="93bdf-107">Multiple Contact Managers are not supported.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="N:System.Net.PeerToPeer" />
  </Docs>
</Namespace>