<Namespace Name="System.IdentityModel.Claims">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="30e32-101"><see cref="N:System.IdentityModel.Claims" /> 名前空間には、Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) クレームベースの ID 承認モデルを実装するクラスが含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-101">The <see cref="N:System.IdentityModel.Claims" /> namespace contains classes that implement the Windows Communication Foundation (WCF) claims-based identity authorization model.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="30e32-102">このモデルには、<see cref="T:System.IdentityModel.Claims.Claim" /> クラスと <see cref="T:System.IdentityModel.Claims.ClaimSet" /> クラスが含まれます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-102">This model includes the <see cref="T:System.IdentityModel.Claims.Claim" /> class and the <see cref="T:System.IdentityModel.Claims.ClaimSet" /> class.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="30e32-103">.NET Framework 4.5 および .NET Framework への Windows Identity Foundation (WIF) の統合以降、WCF のクレームベースの ID モデルは WIF に置き換えられました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-103">Beginning with .NET Framework 4.5 and the integration of Windows Identity Foundation (WIF) into the .NET Framework, the WCF claims-based identity model has been superseded by WIF.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="30e32-104">WIF には、CLR、WCF、および ASP.NET を含む複数の Microsoft 製品スタックでの認証および承認を提供するために使用できるクレーム ベースの ID オブジェクト モデルが用意されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-104">WIF provides a claims-based identity object model that can be used to provide authentication and authorization across several Microsoft product stacks, including the CLR, WCF, and ASP.NET.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="30e32-105">クレーム、クレームの種類、およびクレームに基づく ID とプリンシパルを表す WIF クラスは <see cref="N:System.Security.Claims" /> の名前空間に含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-105">The WIF classes that represent claims, claim types, and identities and principals that are based on claims are contained in the <see cref="N:System.Security.Claims" /> namespace.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="30e32-106">.NET 4.5 以降では、<see cref="N:System.IdentityModel.Claims" /> 名前空間のクラスの代わりにこれらのクラスを使用する必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="30e32-106">Beginning with .NET 4.5, these classes should be used instead of those in the <see cref="N:System.IdentityModel.Claims" /> namespace.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>