<Namespace Name="System.Timers">
  <Docs>
    <summary><span data-ttu-id="7b194-101"><see cref="N:System.Timers" /> 名前空間には、指定した間隔でイベントを発生させることができる <see cref="T:System.Timers.Timer" /> コンポーネントが用意されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-101">The <see cref="N:System.Timers" /> namespace provides the <see cref="T:System.Timers.Timer" /> component, which allows you to raise an event on a specified interval.</span></span></summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="7b194-102"><xref:System.Timers.Timer>コンポーネントは、定期的な間隔を指定することができますサーバー ベースのタイマー、<xref:System.Timers.Timer.Elapsed>イベントは、アプリケーションで発生します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-102">The <xref:System.Timers.Timer> component is a server-based timer, which allows you to specify a recurring interval at which the <xref:System.Timers.Timer.Elapsed> event is raised in your application.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7b194-103">通常の処理を提供するには、このイベントを処理することができますし、します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-103">You can then handle this event to provide regular processing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7b194-104">たとえば、する必要がある重要なサーバーがある場合 24 時間、日、週 7 日間を実行します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-104">For example, suppose you have a critical server that must be kept running 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7b194-105">使用するサービスを作成、<xref:System.Timers.Timer>を定期的にサーバーを確認し、システムが稼働していることを確認してください。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-105">You could create a service that uses a <xref:System.Timers.Timer> to periodically check the server and ensure that the system is up and running.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7b194-106">システムが応答していない場合、サービスでしたしようと、サーバーを再起動するか、管理者に通知します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-106">If the system is not responding, the service could attempt to restart the server or notify an administrator.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="7b194-107">サーバー ベース<xref:System.Timers.Timer>はマルチ スレッド環境でのワーカー スレッドで使用するために設計されています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-107">The server-based <xref:System.Timers.Timer> is designed for use with worker threads in a multithreaded environment.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="7b194-108">サーバーのタイマーは、発生したを処理するスレッド間で移動できます<xref:System.Timers.Timer.Elapsed>時間でイベントの発生時にウィンドウ タイマーは結果として得られるイベント。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="7b194-108">Server timers can move among threads to handle the raised <xref:System.Timers.Timer.Elapsed> event, resulting in more accuracy than Windows timers in raising the event on time.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
  </Docs>
</Namespace>