<Type Name="ImportCatalogPart" FullName="System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart">
  <Metadata>
    <Meta Name="ms.openlocfilehash" Value="17bfe4fc2991ca45ffb31cad133a61b48da42cfa" />
    <Meta Name="ms.sourcegitcommit" Value="d31dc2ede16f6f7bc64e90d9f897ff54c4e3869b" />
    <Meta Name="ms.translationtype" Value="HT" />
    <Meta Name="ms.contentlocale" Value="ja-JP" />
    <Meta Name="ms.lasthandoff" Value="04/03/2018" />
  </Metadata>
  <TypeSignature Language="C#" Value="public sealed class ImportCatalogPart : System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".class public auto ansi sealed beforefieldinit ImportCatalogPart extends System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="DocId" Value="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public NotInheritable Class ImportCatalogPart&#xA;Inherits CatalogPart" />
  <TypeSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public ref class ImportCatalogPart sealed : System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::CatalogPart" />
  <AssemblyInfo>
    <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
    <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
  </AssemblyInfo>
  <Base>
    <BaseTypeName>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart</BaseTypeName>
  </Base>
  <Interfaces />
  <Docs>
    <summary>
      <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-101">あらかじめ定義した設定でコントロールを Web ページに追加できるように、<see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> コントロール (または <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> コントロールとして使用される他の ASP.NET サーバー コントロール) の記述ファイルをインポートします。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="d4f91-101">Imports a description file for a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control (or other ASP.NET server control used as a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control), so that users can add the control to a Web page with pre-defined settings.</span>
      </span>
      <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-102">このクラスは継承できません。</span>
      <span class="sxs-lookup">
        <span data-stu-id="d4f91-102">This class cannot be inherited.</span>
      </span>
    </summary>
    <remarks>
      <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-103"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロールにより、ユーザーに設定を記述する説明ファイルをインポートする、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールやサーバー コントロールに追加するユーザーが、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZoneBase>ゾーンです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-103">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control enables users to import a description file that describes settings on a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control or server control that a user wants to add to a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZoneBase> zone.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-104">ユーザーが、記述ファイルをインポートした後、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>内で、ファイルで参照されているコントロールが表示されます、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>制御、およびユーザーは、ページにコントロールを追加できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-104">After a user imports a description file, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control referenced in the file appears within the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, and a user can add the control to the page.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-105">説明のファイルは、コントロール自体と同じではありません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-105">The description file is not the same as the control itself.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-106">終了する XML ファイルでは、します。Web パーツの拡張機能が名前/値ペア----コントロールの状態を記述するプロパティ値ほとんど含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-106">It is an XML file that ends with a .WebPart extension and contains name/value pairs--mostly property values--that describe the state of the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-107">トピックの説明に従って、指定された XML 形式に従って記述ファイルが作成された[Web パーツ コントロールの記述ファイル](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-107">The description file is created according to a specified XML format, as described in the topic [Web Parts Control Description Files](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-108">Description ファイルを表すコントロールをアセンブリにコンパイルすることができますか、または .ascx ファイルで定義されているユーザー コントロールであることができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-108">As for the control that the description file refers to, it can either be compiled into an assembly, or it can be a user control defined in an .ascx file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-109">どちらの場合、インポートされた記述ファイルで参照されているコントロールは、コントロールをインポートしようとするページをホストする Web サーバーでが必要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-109">In either case, the control referenced in an imported description file must exist on the Web server that hosts the page that is attempting to import the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-110">Description ファイルは、コントロールを含むコントロール名とアセンブリ (またはファイル) を参照し、記述ファイルには、コントロールのプロパティの値、外観、および動作に影響する設定が含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-110">The description file references the control name and the assembly (or file) that contains the control, and the description file contains settings that affect the control's property values, appearance, and behavior.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-111"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロールにより、ユーザーがコントロール上の設定を共有します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-111">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control enables users to share settings on controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-112">複雑なコントロールには、多くのプロパティと設定を持つことができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-112">A complex control can have many properties and settings.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-113">たとえば、カスタム、大規模な企業内の一般的なイントラネット サイトで<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールは、データベース接続、部門別の情報などのユーザーの環境に固有の値を保持するプロパティの数を含めることがあります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-113">For example, in a typical intranet site within a large company, a custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control might contain a number of properties that hold values specific to the users' environment, such as their database connections, departmental information, and so on.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-114">コントロールは、さまざまな外観に影響するプロパティを含むも可能性があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-114">The control might also contain a number of properties that affect its appearance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-115">1 人のユーザーは、特定のサイトのコントロールのカスタマイズ、正しく動作させると、コントロールの記述ファイルをエクスポート、および他のユーザーと、完全に構成されたコントロールをカスタマイズすることが許可されている他のイントラネット サイトを追加するファイルをインポートすることが description ファイルを共有でした。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-115">One user could personalize the control on a particular site and get it working properly, export a description file for the control, and then share the description file with other users, who could import the file to add the fully configured control to other intranet sites that they are allowed to personalize.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-116">そのサイトをホストする Web サーバーで、コンパイルされたアセンブリまたはコントロールを含むユーザー コントロール ファイルが存在する限り、ユーザーは、他の Web サイトにコントロールを追加できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-116">As long as the compiled assembly or user control file containing the control exists on the Web server that is hosting their site, users can add the control to other Web sites.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-117">メカニズムをユーザー ファイルをインポートする説明 (および関連付けられている server が制御するため)、Web ページには、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロールで、ページの開発者が Web ページに追加する必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-117">The mechanism by which users import a description file (and hence its associated server control) into a Web page is the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, which a page developer must add to a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-118">ユーザーが、カタログの表示モードにページを切り替えるときに、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロールが表示され、ユーザーを参照するには、このコントロールで、ユーザーは、します。サーバー コントロールに対応する web パーツの説明ファイルをインポートします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-118">When a user switches the page to catalog display mode, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control appears, and the user can user this control to browse to the .WebPart description file corresponding to the server control they want to import.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-119">UI とにより提供される指示に従って、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール、ユーザーは Web ページの外観およびプロパティが完全に指定されたファイルで構成、インポートされた説明に、目的のサーバー コントロールを追加することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-119">Following the UI and instructions provided by the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, a user is able to add the desired server control into the Web page, with its appearance and properties fully configured as specified in the imported description file.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-120">前に、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールの記述ファイルをインポートできる、ユーザーが (エクスポート) を作成する必要があります最初、ファイルが、既存に基づいて<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-120">Before a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control's description file can be imported, a user must first create (export) the file based on an existing <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-121">次の条件が満たされた場合、コントロールの記述ファイルをエクスポートできます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-121">A description file can be exported for a control if the following conditions are met:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-122">コントロールでマークされたプロパティがある、`Personalizable`属性。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-122">The control has properties marked with the `Personalizable` attribute.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-123">Web.config ファイルが、`enableExport`属性の値に設定`true`上、`<webParts>`要素。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-123">The Web.config file has the `enableExport` attribute value set to `true` on the `<webParts>` element.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-124">開発者は、の値を設定、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A>プロパティの既定値以外の値にコントロールを<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.None>エクスポートを禁止します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-124">A developer sets the value of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> property on the control to a value other than the default value of <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.None>, which prohibits export.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-125">場合、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A>にプロパティの値が設定されている<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.NonSensitiveData>を含む任意のプロパティ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PersonalizableAttribute.IsSensitive%2A>を持つパラメーター、`Personalizable`属性は、ユーザーが記述ファイルをエクスポートする際にエクスポートされません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-125">If the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart.ExportMode%2A> property value is set to <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartExportMode.NonSensitiveData>, any property that contains an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PersonalizableAttribute.IsSensitive%2A> parameter with a `Personalizable` attribute is not exported when a user exports a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-126">これにより、コントロールの開発者を接続文字列などの機密データが特定の状況でエクスポートされることを防ぐためにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-126">This enables control developers to prevent sensitive data, such as connection strings, from being exported in certain situations.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-127">ユーザーが、コントロール、および保存する」の指示に従い、動詞メニューに表示されるエクスポート動詞 をクリックしてエクスポートを有効になっているコントロールをエクスポートします。Web パーツ コントロールのファイルを説明します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-127">A user can export a control that has been enabled for export by clicking the export verb that appears in the verbs menu of the control, and following the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-128">他のユーザーは、コントロールの独自のインスタンスを構成するのには、このファイルをインポートできます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-128">Other users can then import this file to configure their own instances of the control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-129"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスには、いくつかのプロパティが含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-129">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class contains several properties.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-130"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> Description ファイルを検索するを参照するときに、プロパティにはユーザーの手順について説明テキストが含まれます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-130">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property contains text with instructions for users when they browse to locate the description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-131"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>プロパティには内で表示されるように、インポートされたコントロールのラベルとして機能するテキストが含まれています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-131">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property contains text that serves as a label for the imported control as it appears within the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-132"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>コントロールの説明がインポートされているときにエラーが発生した場合に表示されるテキストが含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-132">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> contains text that is displayed if an error occurs when a control description is being imported.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-133"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>プロパティの既定のタイトルを割り当てるの基本プロパティをオーバーライドする<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>開発者は、タイトルを割り当てない場合を制御します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-133">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property overrides the base property to assign a default title for an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control if the developer does not assign a title.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-134"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティには、記述ファイルをアップロードするユーザーがクリックしたボタンのテキストが含まれています。 および<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティには、実際のアップロード処理する方法について説明します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-134">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property contains the text for the button that the user clicks to upload the description file, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property contains the instructions for the upload process.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-135"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスには、いくつかの固有のメソッドも含まれています。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-135">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class also contains several unique methods.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-136"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドの取得、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription>ごとにオブジェクト<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>できるカタログ内のコントロール、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>しなくても、そのインスタンスを作成する各サーバー コントロールに関する情報を表示するコントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-136">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method retrieves a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control in the catalog, which enables an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control to display information about each server control without having to create an instance of it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-137"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>メソッドは、特定のインスタンスを取得<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>メソッドに渡された説明に基づくコントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-137">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method gets an instance of a particular <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, based on the description passed to the method.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-138">使用してに関連するいくつかの本質的なリスクがある、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-138">There are some inherent risks associated with using the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-139">1 つの例は、記述ファイルをインポートするために使用されるを通じて、悪意のあるデータを Web アプリケーションにインポートする可能性です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-139">One example is the possibility of importing malicious data into your Web application through the description files used for importing.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-140">場合他のユーザーが、配置している悪意のあるスクリプト コードの description ファイル内の文字列プロパティの値として、スクリプトをでした可能性のある実行されるときに、ユーザーが記述ファイルをインポートし、Web ページに、参照先のサーバー コントロールを追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-140">If someone has placed malicious script code as the value of a string property in the description file, then that script could potentially be executed when a user imports the description file and adds the referenced server control to a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-141">悪意のあるデータ記述ファイルをインポートするリスクを最小限に抑える、文字列型のプロパティを持つサーバー コントロールではプロパティのデータを常にエンコードする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-141">To minimize the risk of importing description files with malicious data, server controls that have string-typed properties should always encode the property data.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-142">別のリスクには、記述ファイルからの種類のインポートが含まれます (を参照してください[Web パーツ コントロールの記述ファイル](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8))。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-142">Another risk involves importing types through description files (see [Web Parts Control Description Files](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/480992e4-8fc7-43f8-bffc-ae97bbdfe5b8)).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-143">悪意のあるユーザーに多数のアセンブリを読み込む要求を送信できなかった、 <xref:System.AppDomain>、過度な量のメモリが消費されるとなります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-143">A malicious user could submit requests to load many assemblies into the <xref:System.AppDomain>, resulting in an excessive amount of memory being consumed.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-144">インポートに関連するリスクを避けるためを無効にする機能は、まとめてインポート機能を使用していない、または<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-144">To avoid the risks associated with import, you can disable the feature altogether by not using the import feature or the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-145">または、コントロールに対してどのようなユーザーにアクセスを制限することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-145">Or you can limit what users have access to the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-146">これを行うプログラムでは、ロール管理を使用して (を参照してください[承認を使用してロールの管理](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/01954ce4-39a2-487f-8153-a69f6f6f3195))。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-146">You could do this programmatically, using role management (see [Managing Authorization Using Roles](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/01954ce4-39a2-487f-8153-a69f6f6f3195)).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-147">インスタンスのページが読み込まれると、ユーザーが管理者の役割などの特定のロールでかどうかをテストするでした。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-147">For instance, when the page loads, you could test to see whether a user is in a certain role, such as the administrator role.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-148">かどうか、ユーザーは、ロールでは、追加することがプログラムによって、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロールをそのユーザーのページにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-148">If the user is in the role, you could programmatically add the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control to the page for that user.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-149">使用できるユーザーのセットを制限する宣言型の方法を使用することも、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-149">You could also use a declarative approach to limit the set of users that can use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-150">カタログを含む web ページ内で 2 つの配置でした<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone>コントロール: インポートには、ユーザーのいずれかとのことはできません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-150">Within your web page that contains a catalog, you could place two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> controls: one for users who can import, and one for those who cannot.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-151">ユーザーをインポートできますのゾーンには、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-151">The zone for users who can import would contain the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-152">内のゾーン自体を配置する可能性があります、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.LoginView>コントロールで、使用すると、ユーザーまたはロールを指定した認証されたもののみに、ゾーン内のコントロールの使用を制限します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-152">The zone itself could be placed inside of a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.LoginView> control, which would enable you to limit use of the control in the zone to only those authenticated users or roles that you specify.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-153">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> Web ページ上の宣言とプログラムを制御します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-153">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control declaratively and programmatically on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-154">この例では、4 つの部分があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-154">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-155">ユーザー コントロールを Web パーツ ページの表示モードを変更することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-155">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-156">含む Web ページ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone>コントロールと<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-156">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-157">2 つのカスタムを含むソース コード ファイル<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-157">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-158">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときの例の動作の説明。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-158">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-159">このコード例の最初の部分は、ユーザーが Web ページの表示モードを変更できるユーザー コントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-159">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-160">ファイルに次のソース コードを配置し、Displaymodemenucs.ascx または Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (言語に応じて使用している) という名前を付けます必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-160">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-161">詳細については、このコントロールでモードと、ソース コードの説明を表示を参照してください[チュートリアル: Web パーツ ページの表示モードの変更](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-161">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-162">コード例の 2 番目の部分は、Web ページです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-162">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-163">ページの上部には、2 つ`register`ディレクティブ、ユーザー コントロールおよびコンパイル済みのコンポーネントを含む 2 つのカスタム<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-163">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-164">ページがへの参照を宣言型であることを確認、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール、宣言型の要素の適切な階層内に入れ子にします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-164">Notice that the page has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-165">いくつかのプロパティの値は宣言的に割り当てられているにも注意してください、`<asp:importcatalogpart>`要素。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-165">Notice also that several property values are assigned declaratively on the `<asp:importcatalogpart>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-166">また、`Button1_Click`メソッドでプロパティ値の数を更新する、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-166">Also, the `Button1_Click` method updates a number of property values on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-167">ページの <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone>コントロール、2 つのカスタム<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールを宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-167">In the page's <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartZone> control, the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls are declared.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-168">`<aspSample:userinfowebpart>`コントロールが、`exportmode="all"`の属性です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-168">The `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` control has an `exportmode="all"` attribute on it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-169">ユーザー別のユーザー説明ファイルを使用してコントロールをインポートしようとしていますが、インポート可能なコントロールの記述ファイルをエクスポートするには、この属性が必要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-169">This attribute is required to enable users to export a description file for the control, which can then be imported by other users who wish to import the control using the description file.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-170">記述ファイルをエクスポートする Web パーツ アプリケーションのユーザーを有効にする<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>、コントロールを追加して Web アプリケーションのエクスポート機能を有効にすることも必要があります、`enableExport="true"`属性を`<webParts>`要素 (これは、の子`<system.web>`要素)、Web.config ファイルにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-170">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-171">既定で無効なエクスポート、ためまだアプリケーションのエクスポートを有効にない場合、Web.config ファイルを編集し、実行するようになりました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-171">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-172">コード例の 3 番目の部分は、2 つのソース コード<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-172">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-173">これらのコントロールにいくつかのプロパティが付いていることを確認、`WebBrowsable`属性。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-173">Notice that some properties on these controls are marked with the `WebBrowsable` attribute.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-174">これにより、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PropertyGridEditorPart>コントロールを動的に、コントロールが編集モードにする場合は、これらのプロパティを編集するユーザーのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) を生成します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-174">This enables the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PropertyGridEditorPart> control to dynamically generate the user interface (UI) for a user to edit those properties when the controls are in edit mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-175">プロパティが付いているも、`WebDisplayName`編集用の UI 内の各コントロールの横に表示されるラベルのテキストを指定するための属性です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-175">The properties are also marked with a `WebDisplayName` attribute, to specify the text of the label that appears next to each control in the editing UI.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-176">コード例を実行するには、このソース コードをコンパイルする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-176">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-177">コンパイルするには明示的にし、Web サイトの Bin フォルダーまたはグローバル アセンブリ キャッシュに結果として得られるアセンブリを配置できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-177">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-178">またはを動的にコンパイルされる実行時に、サイトの App_Code フォルダー内のソース コードを配置することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-178">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-179">このコード例では、動的なコンパイルを使用します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-179">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-180">両方のコンパイル方法を示すチュートリアルでは、次を参照してください。[チュートリアル: カスタム Web サーバー コントロールの開発と](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-180">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-181">カスタム コントロールと呼ばれる`TextDisplayWebPart`で Web ページで参照される、`<aspSample:TextDisplayWebPart>`要素。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-181">The custom control called `TextDisplayWebPart` is referenced on the Web page with an `<aspSample:TextDisplayWebPart>` element.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-182">その他のコントロールと呼ばれる`UserInfoWebPart`、宣言されて、Web ページで最初に、コントロールの記述ファイルをインポートできることを示す後に削除されますがします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-182">The other control, called `UserInfoWebPart`, is also declared on the Web page initially, though you will remove it later to demonstrate the ability to import a description file for a control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-183">これで、コード例を実行します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-183">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-184">ブラウザーで Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-184">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-185">編集するのには、まず、`UserInfoWebPart`コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-185">The first step is to edit the `UserInfoWebPart` control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-186">使用して、**表示モード**ドロップダウン リスト コントロールを選択**編集**編集モードにページに切り替えます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-186">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Edit** to switch the page to edit mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-187">動詞メニューをクリックして、`UserInfoWebPart`コントロール (タイトル バーに下向きの矢印) をクリックして**編集**です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-187">Click the verbs menu of the `UserInfoWebPart` control (the downward arrow in the title bar), and then click **Edit**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-188">編集用の UI が表示されたら、いくつかの編集コントロールが下に表示されます、`UserInfoWebPart`そのフィールドの値を編集する使用できるコントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-188">When the editing UI appears, several editing controls appear below the `UserInfoWebPart` control that you can use to edit its field values.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-189">一部のフィールドを編集 をクリックして**OK**、しを使用して、**表示モード**をブラウズ モードのページを返すには、ドロップダウンします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-189">Edit some fields, click **OK**, and then use the **Display Mode** drop-down to return the page to browse mode.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-190">2 番目の手順では、エクスポート、します。Web パーツの記述ファイルを`UserInfoWebPart`コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-190">The second step is to export a .WebPart description file for the `UserInfoWebPart` control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-191">(タイトル バーに下向きの矢印で表される)、カスタム コントロールの動詞メニューをクリックし、をクリックして**エクスポート**です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-191">Click the verbs menu on the custom control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-192">保存を指示に従って、します。Web パーツ コントロールのファイルを説明します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-192">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-193">Web ページを閉じてをエディターでページ ソースを編集します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-193">Now close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-194">削除、`<aspSample:userinfowebpart>`宣言要素を制御し、保存してファイルを閉じます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-194">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` control declaration element, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-195">(まだないユーザーをシミュレートするには、この手順を実行している、`UserInfoWebPart`コントロールをページにコントロールをインポートできるように) します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-195">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have the `UserInfoWebPart` control, so you can import the control to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-196">ブラウザーに再度 Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-196">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-197">`UserInfoWebPart`削除したため、コントロールは表示されない必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-197">The `UserInfoWebPart` control should not appear, because you removed it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-198">使用して、**表示モード**ドロップダウン リスト コントロールと選択**カタログ**モードに切り替えるページ カタログ。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-198">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-199"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール をクリックして、**参照**ボタンをクリックしを参照します。Web パーツは、作成したファイルにし、クリックして、**アップロード**ボタンをクリックします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-199">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, and browse to the .WebPart file you created, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-200">コントロールへの参照は、隣のチェック ボックスと共に表示する必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-200">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-201">チェック ボックスを選択し、クリックして**追加**ページにコントロールを追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-201">Select the check box, then click **Add** to add the control to the page.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-202">このページのビューをクリックして、**更新 ImportCatalogPart**プロパティ値の数をプログラムで更新の影響を確認する ページの下部にあるボタン、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-202">While you are in this view of the page, click the **Update ImportCatalogPart** button near the bottom of the page to see the effect of programmatically updating a number of property values on the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-203">ボタンをクリックすると、UI のさまざまなプロパティを変更する方法を確認します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-203">After clicking the button, observe how the various properties are changed in the UI.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-204">最後に、をクリックして**閉じる**カタログ モードを終了し、ページをブラウズ モードを返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-204">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-205">`UserInfoWebPart`以前エクスポートしたときに使用されていた値を含むコントロールがページで、表示されるようになりました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-205">The `UserInfoWebPart` control should now appear in the page, containing the values that it had when you exported it earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
    </remarks>
    <altmember cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.PageCatalogPart" />
    <altmember cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart" />
  </Docs>
  <Members>
    <Member MemberName=".ctor">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public ImportCatalogPart ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig specialname rtspecialname instance void .ctor() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.#ctor" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Sub New ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; ImportCatalogPart();" />
      <MemberType>Constructor</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-206">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> クラスの新しいインスタンスを初期化します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-206">Initializes a new instance of the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> class.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-207"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A>コンス トラクターは、既定値以外のコンス トラクターが宣言されていなければ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスとそのため、不要に特別なタスクが実行されます。 クラスの新しいインスタンスが作成されるときです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-207">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> constructor is a default; no constructor is declared in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class and hence no special tasks are carried out when a new instance of the class is created.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-208">.NET Framework は、クラスのインスタンスを作成するのに内部コンス トラクターを使用します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-208">The .NET Framework uses the constructor internally to create an instance of the class.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-209">通常使用する必要はありません、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A>独自のコードでプログラムでコンス トラクターです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-209">Normally you will not need to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.%23ctor%2A> constructor programmatically in your own code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-210">コントロールの用途では、デザイン時に、ページに宣言によって追加、ページ開発者用です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-210">The intended use of the control is for page developers to add it to a page declaratively at design time.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="BrowseHelpText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string BrowseHelpText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string BrowseHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property BrowseHelpText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ BrowseHelpText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-211">ユーザーに、記述ファイルの場所を参照するように指示するテキスト メッセージを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-211">Gets or sets a text message that instructs users to browse to the location of a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-212">メッセージのテキストを含む文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-212">A string that contains the text of the message.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-213">既定値は、.NET Framework が提供する、カルチャ固有の文字列です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-213">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-214"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A>プロパティは、ユーザー、まず、インポートされたコントロールを追加しているように設定する必要がありますの簡単な概要: パスで入力するか、ファイルを参照して、記述ファイルの場所を指定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-214">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property gives users a simple overview of the first thing they must do in the process of adding an imported control: provide the location of a description file, by either typing in a path or browsing to the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-215">このプロパティのカスタム値を指定する一般的な理由は、記述ファイルを検索するように、参照する必要があります、特定のネットワーク共有など、ユーザーの特別な指示があるかどうかです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-215">A typical reason to supply a custom value for this property is if you have special instructions for users, such as a specific network share to which they should browse to locate a description file.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-216">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-216">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-217">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-217">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-218">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-218">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-219">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-219">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-220">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-220">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-221">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-221">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-222">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-222">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.BrowseHelpText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="CreateChildControls">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void CreateChildControls ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void CreateChildControls() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.CreateChildControls" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub CreateChildControls ()" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void CreateChildControls();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="DefaultButton">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override string DefaultButton { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string DefaultButton" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.DefaultButton" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Property DefaultButton As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual property System::String ^ DefaultButton { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <Attributes>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.ComponentModel.Browsable(false)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.ComponentModel.EditorBrowsable(System.ComponentModel.EditorBrowsableState.Never)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
        <Attribute>
          <AttributeName>System.Web.UI.Themeable(false)</AttributeName>
        </Attribute>
      </Attributes>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-223">ユーザー インターフェイス (UI) で、ボタンを含むフォームがレンダリングされるときにフォーカスを得る既定のボタンとして扱うボタンを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-223">Gets or sets what button in the user interface (UI) is treated as the default button that receives the focus when form that contains the button is rendered.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-224">このプロパティは、ページ開発者コードから呼び出すためのものではありません。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-224">This property is not intended to be called from page developer code.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-225">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> コントロールで既定のフォーカスを受け取る <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel" /> の ID を含む文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-225">A string that contains the ID of the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> that receives the default focus in a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel" /> control.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-226">このプロパティのコードから継承される基本プロパティをオーバーライドする、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel>クラス デザイナーでのプロパティを非表示にし、テーマに影響されるを防ぐことです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-226">The code for this property overrides the base property inherited from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel> class to hide the property from designers and prevent it from being affected by themes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-227">パブリックですが、このプロパティはこのコントロールの既定のレンダリングの設定、Web パーツ コントロールの内部で使用し、ページの開発者によって使用されるものではありません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-227">Though it is public, this property is used internally by the Web Parts control set for default rendering of this control and is not intended to be used by page developers.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-228">このプロパティは、テーマまたはスタイル シート テーマによって設定することはできません。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-228">This property cannot be set by themes or style sheet themes.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-229">詳細については、次を参照してください。<xref:System.Web.UI.ThemeableAttribute>と[ASP.NET のテーマとスキン](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/5df3ebbd-d46c-4502-9406-02f9df4ef2c3)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-229">For more information, see <xref:System.Web.UI.ThemeableAttribute> and [ASP.NET Themes and Skins](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/5df3ebbd-d46c-4502-9406-02f9df4ef2c3).</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <altmember cref="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Panel.DefaultButton" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig virtual instance class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Function GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions () As WebPartDescriptionCollection" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; override System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPartDescriptionCollection ^ GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-230">カタログ内で利用できる <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> コントロールの説明のコレクションを返します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-230">Returns a collection of descriptions of the available <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> controls in a catalog.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-231">カタログ内の各コントロールの <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection" /> を含む <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-231">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescriptionCollection" /> that contains a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> for each control in a catalog.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-232"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>で抽象基本メソッドが宣言されているために、メソッドは実装を提供、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart>クラスです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-232">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method provides an implementation for the abstract base method declared in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogPart> class.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-233"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドは、カタログの各コントロールの説明情報を返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-233">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method returns description information for each control in a catalog.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-234">場合に注意してください、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>制御を使用できます 1 台のサーバー コントロール カタログで、一度に場合でも、複数のコントロールがあった場合、メソッドは機能します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-234">Note that in the case of an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, there can be only one server control in the catalog at a time, even though the method would work if there were multiple controls.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-235">A<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription>がに関する重要な情報を含むオブジェクトでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール、その ID では、コントロール、およびから継承されているいくつかの重要なプロパティの値へのオブジェクト参照を含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part>クラスなど<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A>と<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-235">A <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object is an object that contains essential information about a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control, including its ID, an object reference to the control, and the values of several important properties that are inherited from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part> class, such as <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Title%2A> and <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.Part.Description%2A>.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-236"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドのパフォーマンスが向上します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-236">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method improves performance.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-237">カタログが作成されると、一部の情報が含まれている、タイトル、説明、アイコン (が存在する場合)、および ID を含む各コントロールについて、必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-237">When a catalog is created, it needs some information about each control it contains, including a title, a description, an icon (if one exists), and an ID.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-238">この情報を取得するには、各コントロールのインスタンスを作成する必要はなく、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase>呼び出しのカタログを作成するゾーン、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッド、および呼び出しは、コントロールのインスタンスではなく、コントロールの説明情報のみを返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-238">Rather than having to create an instance of each control to get this information, a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZoneBase> zone that creates a catalog calls the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method, and the call returns only the description information for the control rather than an instance of the control.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-239">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> Web ページ上のメソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-239">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-240">この例では、4 つの部分があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-240">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-241">ユーザー コントロールを Web パーツ ページの表示モードを変更することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-241">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-242">含む Web ページ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone>コントロールと<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コードを使用すると、コントロール、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-242">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, along with code that uses the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-243">2 つのカスタムを含むソース コード ファイル<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-243">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-244">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときの例の動作の説明。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-244">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-245">このコード例の最初の部分は、ユーザーが Web ページの表示モードを変更できるユーザー コントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-245">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-246">ファイルに次のソース コードを配置し、Displaymodemenucs.ascx または Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (言語に応じて使用している) という名前を付けます必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-246">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-247">詳細については、このコントロールでモードと、ソース コードの説明を表示を参照してください[チュートリアル: Web パーツ ページの表示モードの変更](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-247">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-248">コード例の 2 番目の部分は、Web ページです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-248">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-249">ページの上部には、2 つ`register`ディレクティブ、ユーザー コントロールおよびコンパイル済みのコンポーネントを含む 2 つのカスタム<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-249">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-250">これらのコントロールは、ページのマークアップで宣言によって参照されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-250">Both of these controls are referenced declaratively in the markup of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-251">宣言型の参照で、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール (から始まる、`aspSample`プレフィックス)、それぞれが、`exportMode="all"`属性を追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-251">On the declarative references to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls (both begin with an `aspSample` prefix), note that each has an `exportMode="all"` attribute added to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-252">この属性では、エクスポートすることができます、します。ページにコントロールをインポートするためのステップを後で使用すると、コントロールの web パーツの説明ファイルです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-252">This attribute enables you to export a .WebPart description file for the control, which you will use in a later to step to import the control to a page.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-253">記述ファイルをエクスポートする Web パーツ アプリケーションのユーザーを有効にする<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>、コントロールを追加して Web アプリケーションのエクスポート機能を有効にすることも必要があります、`enableExport="true"`属性を`<webParts>`要素 (これは、の子`<system.web>`要素)、Web.config ファイルにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-253">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-254">既定で無効なエクスポート、ためまだアプリケーションのエクスポートを有効にない場合、Web.config ファイルを編集し、実行するようになりました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-254">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-255">Web ページにもへの参照を宣言、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール、宣言型の要素の適切な階層内に入れ子にします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-255">The Web page also has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-256"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>のコード内でメソッドが呼び出された、`Button1_Click`メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-256">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method is called within the code for the `Button1_Click` method.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/ImportCatalogPart_GetCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/ImportCatalogPart_GetVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-257">コード例の 3 番目の部分は、2 つのソース コード<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-257">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-258">コード例を実行するには、このソース コードをコンパイルする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-258">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-259">コンパイルするには明示的にし、Web サイトの Bin フォルダーまたはグローバル アセンブリ キャッシュに結果として得られるアセンブリを配置できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-259">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-260">またはを動的にコンパイルされる実行時に、サイトの App_Code フォルダー内のソース コードを配置することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-260">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-261">このコード例では、動的なコンパイルを使用します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-261">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-262">両方のコンパイル方法を示すチュートリアルでは、次を参照してください。[チュートリアル: カスタム Web サーバー コントロールの開発と](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-262">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-263">これで、コード例を実行します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-263">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-264">ブラウザーで Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-264">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-265">最初の手順では、エクスポート、します。各 web パーツの説明ファイル<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール (用、`TextDisplayWebPart`との`UserInfoWebPart`コントロール)。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-265">The first step is export a .WebPart description file for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control (for the `TextDisplayWebPart` and for the `UserInfoWebPart` control).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-266">各コントロールの (タイトル バーに下向きの矢印によって表される)、コントロールの動詞メニューをクリックし、をクリックして**エクスポート**です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-266">For each control, click the verbs menu on the control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-267">保存を指示に従って、します。Web パーツ コントロールのファイルを説明します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-267">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-268">各コントロールの記述ファイルをエクスポートした後は、Web ページを閉じてエディターでページ ソースを編集します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-268">After you have exported a description file for each control, close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-269">削除、`<aspSample:userinfowebpart>`と`<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>`宣言要素を制御、保存して、ファイルを閉じます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-269">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` and the `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` control declaration elements, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-270">(まだないこれらのコントロールをページにコントロールをインポートできるようにするユーザーをシミュレートするには、この手順を行っている。)</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-270">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have these controls, so you can import the controls to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-271">ブラウザーに再度 Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-271">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-272">使用して、**表示モード**ドロップダウン リスト コントロールと選択**カタログ**モードに切り替えるページ カタログ。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-272">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-273"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール をクリックして、**参照** ボタンをクリックしを参照してください、します。作成した web パーツ ファイルは、1 つを選択し、クリックして、**アップロード**ボタンをクリックします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-273">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, browse to the .WebPart files you created, select one, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-274">コントロールへの参照は、隣のチェック ボックスと共に表示する必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-274">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-275">チェック ボックスを選択し、クリックして**追加**ページにコントロールを追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-275">Select the check box, then click **Add** to add the control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-276">別のコントロールには、このプロセスを繰り返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-276">Repeat this process for the other control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-277">このページのビューをクリックして、 **web パーツの説明を取得**プログラムでアクセスするための影響を確認する ページの下部にあるボタンをクリック、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription>オブジェクトにコントロールの説明が現在読み込まれているため、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-277">While you are in this view of the page, click the **Get WebPart Description** button near the bottom of the page to see the effect of programmatically accessing the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object for the control description currently loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-278">については、説明の詳細へのアクセスに使用する方法、`Button1_Click`ページのソースのメソッドは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-278">The method used to access the description details, found in the `Button1_Click` method of the page source, is the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-279">ボタンの下にラベルは、コントロールに関する基本情報を表示します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-279">A label below the button displays basic details about the control.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-280">最初のコントロールを追加すると、プロセスを繰り返して、2 つ目のコントロールをページに追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-280">After adding the first control, repeat the process to add the second control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-281">最後に、をクリックして**閉じる**カタログ モードを終了し、ページをブラウズ モードを返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-281">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-282">両方のカスタム コントロール ページで、前の記述ファイルにエクスポートしたときの値を含む表示されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-282">Both custom controls should now appear in the page, containing the values they had when you exported description files earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="GetWebPart">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart GetWebPart (System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription description);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method public hidebysig virtual instance class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart GetWebPart(class System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription description) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart(System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Function GetWebPart (description As WebPartDescription) As WebPart" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; override System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPart ^ GetWebPart(System::Web::UI::WebControls::WebParts::WebPartDescription ^ description);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="description" Type="System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="description">
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-283">コントロールに関する詳細を格納している <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" />。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-283">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> that contains details about the control.</span>
          </span>
        </param>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-284">メソッドに渡される説明の値に基づいて、<see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> コントロールへの参照を返します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-284">Returns a reference to a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control based on the values in the description passed into the method.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <returns>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-285">説明が <paramref name="description" /> の値に一致する <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> コントロール。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-285">A <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart" /> control whose description matches the values in <paramref name="description" />.</span>
          </span>
        </returns>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-286"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>メソッドへの参照を返します、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>詳細を説明の値に一致するコントロール、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription>メソッドに渡されたオブジェクト。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-286">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method returns a reference to a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control whose description details match the values of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> object passed into the method.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-287">通常、このメソッドはと共に使用、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A>メソッドで、カタログ内のコントロールの説明を取得するために使用します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-287">Typically, this method is used together with the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.DeclarativeCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions%2A> method, which is used to retrieve the descriptions of controls in the catalog.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-288">各<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールは、取得または個別に渡すことによって、必要に応じて操作<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription>オブジェクトを<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-288">Individual <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls can then be retrieved or manipulated as needed by passing individual <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription> objects to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-289">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、 <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> Web ページ上のメソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-289">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-290">この例では、4 つの部分があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-290">The example has four parts:</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-291">ユーザー コントロールを Web パーツ ページの表示モードを変更することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-291">A user control that enables you to change display modes on a Web Parts page.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-292">含む Web ページ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone>コントロールと<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コードを使用すると、コントロール、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-292">A Web page that contains a <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.CatalogZone> control and an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, along with code that uses the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-293">2 つのカスタムを含むソース コード ファイル<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-293">A source code file that contains two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span>  
  
-   <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-294">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときの例の動作の説明。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-294">An explanation of how the example works when you load the page in a browser.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-295">このコード例の最初の部分は、ユーザーが Web ページの表示モードを変更できるユーザー コントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-295">The first part of this code example is the user control that enables users to change display modes on a Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-296">ファイルに次のソース コードを配置し、Displaymodemenucs.ascx または Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (言語に応じて使用している) という名前を付けます必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-296">You should place the following source code in a file and name it Displaymodemenucs.ascx or Displaymodemenuvb.ascx (depending on which language you are using).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-297">詳細については、このコントロールでモードと、ソース コードの説明を表示を参照してください[チュートリアル: Web パーツ ページの表示モードの変更](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-297">For details about display modes and a description of the source code in this control, see [Walkthrough: Changing Display Modes on a Web Parts Page](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/24e42f74-82dc-4c13-8574-130398985fc0).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/DisplayModeMenuCS.ascx#7)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#7](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/DisplayModeMenuVB.ascx#7)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-298">コード例の 2 番目の部分は、Web ページです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-298">The second part of the code example is the Web page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-299">ページの上部には、2 つ`register`ディレクティブ、ユーザー コントロールおよびコンパイル済みのコンポーネントを含む 2 つのカスタム<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-299">At the top of the page are two `register` directives, one for the user control and one for the compiled component that contains the two custom <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-300">これらのコントロールは、ページのマークアップで宣言によって参照されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-300">Both of these controls are referenced declaratively in the markup of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-301">宣言型の参照で、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール (から始まる、`aspSample`プレフィックス)、それぞれが、`exportMode="all"`属性を追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-301">On the declarative references to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls (both begin with an `aspSample` prefix), note that each has an `exportMode="all"` attribute added to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-302">この属性では、エクスポートすることができます、します。ページにコントロールをインポートするためのステップを後で使用すると、コントロールの web パーツの説明ファイルです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-302">This attribute enables you to export a .WebPart description file for the control, which you will use in a later to step to import the control to a page.</span></span>  
  
> [!NOTE]
>  <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-303">記述ファイルをエクスポートする Web パーツ アプリケーションのユーザーを有効にする<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>、コントロールを追加して Web アプリケーションのエクスポート機能を有効にすることも必要があります、`enableExport="true"`属性を`<webParts>`要素 (これは、の子`<system.web>`要素)、Web.config ファイルにします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-303">To enable users of a Web Parts application to export a description file for <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls, you must also enable the export feature in the Web application by adding an `enableExport="true"` attribute to the `<webParts>` element (which is a child of the `<system.web>` element) in the Web.config file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-304">既定で無効なエクスポート、ためまだアプリケーションのエクスポートを有効にない場合、Web.config ファイルを編集し、実行するようになりました。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-304">Export is disabled by default, so if you have not yet enabled export for your application, edit the Web.config file and do it now.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-305">Web ページにもへの参照を宣言、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール、宣言型の要素の適切な階層内に入れ子にします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-305">The Web page also has a declarative reference to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, nested within the proper hierarchy of declarative elements.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-306"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>のコード内でメソッドが呼び出された、`Button2_Click`メソッドです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-306">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method is called within the code for the `Button2_Click` method.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/ImportCatalogPart_GetCS.aspx#1)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#1](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/ImportCatalogPart_GetVB.aspx#1)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-307">コード例の 3 番目の部分は、2 つのソース コード<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-307">The third part of the code example is the source code for the two <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> controls.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-308">コード例を実行するには、このソース コードをコンパイルする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-308">For the code example to run, you must compile this source code.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-309">コンパイルするには明示的にし、Web サイトの Bin フォルダーまたはグローバル アセンブリ キャッシュに結果として得られるアセンブリを配置できます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-309">You can compile it explicitly and put the resulting assembly in your Web site's Bin folder or the global assembly cache.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-310">またはを動的にコンパイルされる実行時に、サイトの App_Code フォルダー内のソース コードを配置することができます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-310">Alternatively, you can put the source code in your site's App_Code folder, where it will be dynamically compiled at run time.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-311">このコード例では、動的なコンパイルを使用します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-311">This code example uses dynamic compilation.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-312">両方のコンパイル方法を示すチュートリアルでは、次を参照してください。[チュートリアル: カスタム Web サーバー コントロールの開発と](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08)です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-312">For a walkthrough that demonstrates both methods of compiling, see [Walkthrough: Developing and Using a Custom Web Server Control](http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/6d90782a-a1a4-45a6-b2d4-cf6362b83b08).</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/CS/userinfowebpart.cs#6)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get#6](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Get/VB/userinfowebpart.vb#6)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-313">これで、コード例を実行します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-313">Now run the code example.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-314">ブラウザーで Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-314">Load the Web page in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-315">最初の手順では、エクスポート、します。各 web パーツの説明ファイル<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロール (用、`TextDisplayWebPart`との`UserInfoWebPart`コントロール)。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-315">The first step is export a .WebPart description file for each <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control (for the `TextDisplayWebPart` and for the `UserInfoWebPart` control).</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-316">各コントロールの (タイトル バーに下向きの矢印によって表される)、コントロールの動詞メニューをクリックし、をクリックして**エクスポート**です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-316">For each control, click the verbs menu on the control (represented by the downward arrow in the title bar), and click **Export**.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-317">保存を指示に従って、します。Web パーツ コントロールのファイルを説明します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-317">Follow the instructions to save a .WebPart description file for the control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-318">各コントロールの記述ファイルをエクスポートした後は、Web ページを閉じてエディターでページ ソースを編集します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-318">After you have exported a description file for each control, close the Web page, and edit the page source in an editor.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-319">削除、`<aspSample:userinfowebpart>`と`<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>`宣言要素を制御、保存して、ファイルを閉じます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-319">Delete the `<aspSample:userinfowebpart>` and the `<aspSample:textdisplaywebpart>` control declaration elements, then save and close the file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-320">(まだないこれらのコントロールをページにコントロールをインポートできるようにするユーザーをシミュレートするには、この手順を行っている。)</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-320">(You are doing this step to simulate a user who does not yet have these controls, so you can import the controls to the page).</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-321">ブラウザーに再度 Web ページを読み込みます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-321">Load the Web page again in a browser.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-322">使用して、**表示モード**ドロップダウン リスト コントロールと選択**カタログ**モードに切り替えるページ カタログ。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-322">Use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control and select **Catalog** to switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-323"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール をクリックして、**参照** ボタンをクリックしを参照してください、します。作成した web パーツ ファイルは、1 つを選択し、クリックして、**アップロード**ボタンをクリックします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-323">In the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Browse** button, browse to the .WebPart files you created, select one, then click the **Upload** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-324">コントロールへの参照は、隣のチェック ボックスと共に表示する必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-324">A reference to the control should appear with a check box next to it.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-325">コントロールの説明をアップロードするようになりました、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール をクリックして、**使用 GetWebPart**ページの下部にあるボタンをクリックします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-325">Now that the control description is uploaded to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control, click the **Use GetWebPart** button near the bottom of the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-326">呼び出す場合の効果を示しますこの、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>メソッドおよびで現在読み込まれているコントロールの説明を渡す、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-326">This will demonstrate the effect of calling the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method and passing to it the control description currently loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-327">関連付けられたサーバー コントロールが追加すぐに Web ページにユーザーがクリックしてしなくても、**追加**ボタンをクリックします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-327">Note that the associated server control is added immediately to the Web page, without the user having to click the **Add** button.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-328"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A>で呼び出されるメソッド、`Button2_Click`ページのソースのメソッドを返します、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>に読み込まれている現在の説明に関連付けられたコントロール、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-328">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetWebPart%2A> method, which is called in the `Button2_Click` method of the page source, returns the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control associated with the current description that is loaded in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-329">[次へ]、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager.AddWebPart%2A>メソッドを呼び出すと、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart>コントロールがページに直接追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-329">Next the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartManager.AddWebPart%2A> method is called, and the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPart> control is directly added to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-330">これからプログラムによってコントロールを追加する方法を示して、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>ユーザーの介入なしのコントロールです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-330">This demonstrates how to add a control programmatically from the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control without user intervention.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-331">最初のコントロールを追加すると、プロセスを繰り返して、2 つ目のコントロールをページに追加します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-331">After adding the first control, repeat the process to add the second control to the page.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-332">最後に、をクリックして**閉じる**カタログ モードを終了し、ページをブラウズ モードを返します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-332">Finally, click **Close** to exit catalog mode and return the page to browse mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-333">両方のカスタム コントロール ページで、前の記述ファイルにエクスポートしたときの値を含む表示されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-333">Both custom controls should now appear in the page, containing the values they had when you exported description files earlier.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentNullException">
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-334">
            <paramref name="description" /> は <see langword="null" />です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-334">
              <paramref name="description" /> is <see langword="null" />.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <exception cref="T:System.ArgumentException">
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-335">
            <paramref name="description" /> が、使用できる <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> 値ではありません。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-335">
              <paramref name="description" /> is not an available <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.WebPartDescription" /> value.</span>
          </span>
        </exception>
        <altmember cref="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.GetAvailableWebPartDescriptions" />
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="ImportedPartLabelText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string ImportedPartLabelText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string ImportedPartLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property ImportedPartLabelText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ ImportedPartLabelText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-336">ユーザーが記述ファイルをインポートした後に表示されるテキストを取得または設定します。これは、インポートされたコントロールのカタログ内で個別のインポート済みコントロールを表現または説明するためのテキストです。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-336">Gets or sets text displayed after a user imports a description file to represent or describe the imported control within the catalog of imported controls.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-337">ラベルのテキストを含む文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-337">A string that contains the text of the label.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-338">既定値は、.NET Framework が提供する、カルチャ固有の文字列です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-338">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-339"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>に含まれるコントロールを説明する短い、一般的なラベルを格納するプロパティが使用される通常の<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-339">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property is typically used to contain a short, general label that describes the control contained in the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-340">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-340">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-341">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-341">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-342">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-342">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-343">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-343">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-344">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-344">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-345">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-345">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-346">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-346">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.ImportedPartLabelText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="LoadControlState">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void LoadControlState (object savedState);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void LoadControlState(object savedState) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.LoadControlState(System.Object)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub LoadControlState (savedState As Object)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void LoadControlState(System::Object ^ savedState);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="savedState" Type="System.Object" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="savedState">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="OnInit">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void OnInit (EventArgs e);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void OnInit(class System.EventArgs e) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.OnInit(System.EventArgs)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub OnInit (e As EventArgs)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void OnInit(EventArgs ^ e);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="e" Type="System.EventArgs" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="e">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="PartImportErrorLabelText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string PartImportErrorLabelText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string PartImportErrorLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property PartImportErrorLabelText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ PartImportErrorLabelText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-347">インポート プロセスでエラーが発生した場合に表示されるエラー メッセージを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-347">Gets or sets an error message that is displayed if an error occurs during the import process.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-348">ラベルのテキストを含む文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-348">A string that contains the text of the label.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-349">既定値は、.NET Framework が提供する、カルチャ固有の文字列です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-349">The default value is a culture-specific message supplied by the .NET Framework.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-350"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>プロパティはいくつかの問題またはエラーが発生した場合、ページの説明ファイルをインポートしようとしました。 ユーザーに通知するために役立ちます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-350">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property is useful for notifying a user if some problem or error occurs while the page attempts to import a description file.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-351">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-351">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-352">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-352">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-353">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-353">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-354">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-354">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-355">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-355">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-356">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-356">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-357">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-357">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.PartImportErrorLabelText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Render">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void Render (System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void Render(class System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Render(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub Render (writer As HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void Render(System::Web::UI::HtmlTextWriter ^ writer);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="writer" Type="System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="writer">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="RenderContents">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override void RenderContents (System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer);" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance void RenderContents(class System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter writer) cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.RenderContents(System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Sub RenderContents (writer As HtmlTextWriter)" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override void RenderContents(System::Web::UI::HtmlTextWriter ^ writer);" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Void</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters>
        <Parameter Name="writer" Type="System.Web.UI.HtmlTextWriter" />
      </Parameters>
      <Docs>
        <param name="writer">To be added.</param>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="SaveControlState">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="protected internal override object SaveControlState ();" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".method familyorassemblyhidebysig virtual instance object SaveControlState() cil managed" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="M:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.SaveControlState" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Protected Friend Overrides Function SaveControlState () As Object" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="protected public:&#xA; override System::Object ^ SaveControlState();" />
      <MemberType>Method</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.Object</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Parameters />
      <Docs>
        <summary>To be added.</summary>
        <returns>To be added.</returns>
        <remarks>To be added.</remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="Title">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public override string Title { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string Title" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Overrides Property Title As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; virtual property System::String ^ Title { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-358">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> コントロールのタイトル バーに表示されるタイトルを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-358">Gets or sets the title that appears in the title bar of an <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart" /> control.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-359">コントロールのタイトルとして使用される文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-359">A string that is used as the title of the control.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-360">既定値は、Web パーツ コントロール セットによって提供される、計算済みのコントロール名です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-360">The default value is a calculated control name supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-361"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>プロパティの値がのタイトル バーに表示される、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>ときに、コントロールは、カタログのモードで表示を制御します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-361">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is displayed in the title bar of an <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control when the control is visible in catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-362">使用して、プロパティの値を設定するには、コントロールがページで宣言されている場合、`Title`属性。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-362">When the control is declared in a page, you can set a value for the property by using the `Title` attribute.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-363">タイトルの値を指定しない、このコントロールでユーザーが編集できるプロパティの種類を記述する、カルチャに固有の既定値が使用されます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-363">If you do not supply a value for the title, a culture-specific default value is used to describe the kind of properties that this control allows users to edit.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-364">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-364">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-365">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-365">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-366">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-366">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-367">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-367">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-368">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-368">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-369">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-369">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-370">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-370">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.Title%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="UploadButtonText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string UploadButtonText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string UploadButtonText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property UploadButtonText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ UploadButtonText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-371">記述ファイルのアップロードを開始する <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> コントロールのテキストを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-371">Gets or sets the text for the <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> control that initiates the upload of a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-372">
            <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" /> のテキストとして使用される文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-372">A string that is used as the text for a <see cref="T:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button" />.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-373">既定値は、Web パーツ コントロール セットによって提供されるカルチャ固有の文字列です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-373">The default value is a culture-specific string supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-374"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティのテキストを提供する、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button>アップロード プロセスを開始するコントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-374">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property provides the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.Button> control that initiates the upload process.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-375">このプロパティは、または、カスタム テキストを割り当てるかどうか、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティのテキストをユーザーが記述ファイルをアップロードすることが明確にする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-375">If you assign custom text to this property, or to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property, the text should make clear that the user is uploading a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-376">テキストは必要がありますいない言うまたはアップロード プロセスが実際には、コントロール自体をアップロードすることを意味します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-376">The text should not say or imply that the upload process is actually uploading the control itself.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-377">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-377">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-378">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-378">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-379">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-379">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-380">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-380">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-381">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-381">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-382">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-382">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-383">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-383">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
    <Member MemberName="UploadHelpText">
      <MemberSignature Language="C#" Value="public string UploadHelpText { get; set; }" />
      <MemberSignature Language="ILAsm" Value=".property instance string UploadHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="DocId" Value="P:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText" />
      <MemberSignature Language="VB.NET" Value="Public Property UploadHelpText As String" />
      <MemberSignature Language="C++ CLI" Value="public:&#xA; property System::String ^ UploadHelpText { System::String ^ get(); void set(System::String ^ value); };" />
      <MemberType>Property</MemberType>
      <AssemblyInfo>
        <AssemblyName>System.Web</AssemblyName>
        <AssemblyVersion>4.0.0.0</AssemblyVersion>
      </AssemblyInfo>
      <ReturnValue>
        <ReturnType>System.String</ReturnType>
      </ReturnValue>
      <Docs>
        <summary>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-384">ユーザーに記述ファイルをアップロードする方法を通知するメッセージのテキストを取得または設定します。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-384">Gets or sets the text of the message that tells the user how to upload a description file.</span>
          </span>
        </summary>
        <value>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-385">ユーザーが記述ファイルをアップロードするときの指示として使用される文字列。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-385">A string that is used as instructions for the user to upload a description file.</span>
          </span>
          <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-386">既定値は、Web パーツ コントロール セットによって提供されるカルチャ固有の文字列です。</span>
          <span class="sxs-lookup">
            <span data-stu-id="d4f91-386">The default value is a culture-specific string supplied by the Web Parts control set.</span>
          </span>
        </value>
        <remarks>
          <format type="text/markdown"><![CDATA[  
  
## Remarks  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-387"><xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティは、簡単な文や指示 description ファイルをアップロードするためのボタンをクリックして、ユーザーに対する命令の語句を提供します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-387">The <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property provides a brief sentence or phrase of instructions for users, telling them to click a button to upload the description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-388">このプロパティは、または、カスタム テキストを割り当てるかどうか、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A>プロパティのテキストをユーザーが記述ファイルをアップロードすることが明確にする必要があります。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-388">If you assign custom text to this property, or to the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadButtonText%2A> property, the text should make clear that the user is uploading a description file.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-389">テキストは必要がありますいない言うまたはアップロード プロセスが実際には、コントロール自体をアップロードすることを意味します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-389">The text should not say or imply that the upload process is actually uploading the control itself.</span></span>  
  
   
  
## Examples  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-390">次のコード例を使用する方法を示しています、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティをプログラムで宣言します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-390">The following code example demonstrates how to use the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property declaratively and programmatically.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-391">完全なコードと、例を実行するために必要な手順の例」のセクションを参照してください。、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>クラスの概要です。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-391">For the full code and instructions required to run the example, see the Example section of the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> class overview.</span></span>  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-392">コードの次のセクションでは、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>コントロールのプロパティ値が宣言して設定します。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-392">In the following section of code, notice that the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property value is set declaratively for the control.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-aspx-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#2)]
 [!code-aspx-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#2](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#2)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-393">コードのこのセクションで、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティの値がプログラムによって割り当てられます。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-393">In this section of code, the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property value is assigned programmatically.</span></span>  
  
 [!code-csharp[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/csharp/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/CS/ImportCatalogPartOverviewCS.aspx#3)]
 [!code-vb[WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview#3](~/samples/snippets/visualbasic/VS_Snippets_WebNet/WebParts_ImportCatalogPart_Overview/VB/ImportCatalogPartOverviewVB.aspx#3)]  
  
 <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-394">ブラウザーでページを読み込むときに行うこともできます、**表示モード**選択するドロップダウン リスト コントロール**カタログ モード**カタログ モードに切り替えるとします。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-394">When you load the page in a browser, you can use the **Display Mode** drop-down list control to select **Catalog Mode** and switch the page to catalog mode.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-395">カタログ モードやアップロード description ファイル内のページでのユーザー インターフェイス (UI) に表示されるさまざまなテキスト文字列をメモ、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart>コントロール。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-395">With the page in catalog mode and the description file uploaded, note the various text strings displayed in the user interface (UI) for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart> control.</span></span> <span data-ttu-id="d4f91-396">クリックした場合、**記述ファイルのアップロード**ボタン、ui プロパティをいくつかのテキストを変更するのテキストを含む、<xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A>プロパティです。</span><span class="sxs-lookup"><span data-stu-id="d4f91-396">If you click the **Upload Description File** button, the text for several of the properties in the UI is changed, including the text for the <xref:System.Web.UI.WebControls.WebParts.ImportCatalogPart.UploadHelpText%2A> property.</span></span>  
  
 ]]></format>
        </remarks>
      </Docs>
    </Member>
  </Members>
</Type>